Edwin B. Rollins Papers MS054
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1850 -- 1961; 1930 -- 1955; MS054.003; 0.5 Linear Feet; 565 Digital Object(s)
  - Engine room in Tufts' power house, 1905; MS054.003.DO.02595; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Edwin B. Rollins, papers; Interior views; copy negative
  - Patrick Burns, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02596; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Pansy Park, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02597; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Paige Hall, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02598; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Packard Hall, MS054.003.DO.02599; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Packard Hall and part of Bendetson Hall, 1948; MS054.003.DO.02600; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Open-air gymnasium, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02601; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Nightshirt parade, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02602; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Events; Nightshirt Parade; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - The Knight house before alterations, 1938; MS054.003.DO.02603; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Original interior of the Mechanical Engineering Laboratory, 1925; MS054.003.DO.02608; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Laboratories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Dept. of Mechanical Engineering
  - Representation of Yale's mammoth tent, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02609; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Tufts theatre, MS054.003.DO.02610; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Theater; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Dept. of Drama
  - Actor in performance, MS054.003.DO.02611; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Chester mystery plays, 1850 -- 1950; MS054.003.DO.02612; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Theater; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Robinson Hall Dynamo Room, 1947; MS054.003.DO.02613; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Slides and negatives rom Prof. Rollins. Donated September 1967."
    Laboratories; Rooms; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Dept. of Electrical Engineering
  - Balcony in Room 16 of Robinson Hall with magneto telephone equipment in rear, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02614; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Balcony, overhead lamp banks, and the direct current motor-generator sets located in Room 17 of Robinson Hall, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02615; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Robinson Hall, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02616; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Robinson Hall, 1945; MS054.003.DO.02617; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Robinson Hall with Hodgdon Gate in the foreground, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02618; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Academic; Gates; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Classroom in Robinson Hall, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02619; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Laboratory in Robinson Hall, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02620; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory, 1947; MS054.003.DO.02621; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Interior of Jackson Gymnasium, 1905; MS054.003.DO.02622; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Backstage in Jackson Gymnasium, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02623; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Exterior of Jackson Gymnasium, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02624; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The Rez, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02625; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Reservoirs; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of The Reservoir and pump house, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02626; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Parking lot where The Reservoir once stood, 1945; MS054.003.DO.02627; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Telephone office in Robinson Hall, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02628; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Telephone office in Robinson Hall, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02629; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Tilton Hall, 1961; MS054.003.DO.02630; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Campus trees with Goddard Chapel in the background, MS054.003.DO.02631; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The 1959 avenue, MS054.003.DO.02632; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Ice damage to poplar trees, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02633; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unidentified house, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02901; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Blakeley Hall accross the playing field from Professors Row, 1935; MS054.003.DO.02902; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; Buildings; Dormitories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Two unidentified people standing on the top of a hill, MS054.003.DO.02903; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Views; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - The Gate House with West Hall and the Academic Quad in the background, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02904; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Views of cars parked along street, 1960; MS054.003.DO.02905; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - View of hillside near campus, 1960; MS054.003.DO.02906; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - View of students walking accross bridge at the corner of College and Boston Avenues, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02907; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    People; Students; Views; Bridges (built works); Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of students with Cousens Gymnasium in the background, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02908; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    People; Students; Buildings; Gymnasiums; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - The razing of the Rez with West Hall in the background, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02909; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Views; Buildings; Dormitories; Reservoirs; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - The razing of the Rez with West Hall in the background, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02910; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
  - View of Cousens Gymnasium, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02911; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)
    Views; Buildings; Gymnasiums; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02912; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 43)